<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-03-16T21:13:25-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Hidden Ones</title><subtitle></subtitle><author><name>esac-io</name></author><entry><title type="html">Hello world</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/2020/03/15/hello-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello world" /><published>2020-03-15T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-03-15T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/2020/03/15/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/2020/03/15/hello-world.html">&lt;p&gt;Well, everyone knows how hard writing can be (even more challenging in
another language far aside from you mother one), so this is a attempt to
improve this particular skill, and spread some information in the data
sea which currently compose majority of &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;VIRTUALITY&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yes, this &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;artificial&lt;/code&gt; world who surrounding our existence is
growing in exponential rates, the virtual interface will be the
only bridge to access the present, understand the pass, unveil the
future, the final interlink, no more prisons for the mind,
no more insignificant worlds to conquer, a free singularity,
a clear horizon blossoming in the dawn breeze,
nothing and everything at the same time, existential detachment
history, the new paradigm that will obliterate every
obsolete obstacle in its path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Aw. I lost my train of thought here.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog will certainly come in hand to achieve this minor goal
and a lot of friends advise me to have some online presence,
so you are welcome, beware though, this articles are just daydreams
from a troubled, disruptive inner eye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;And where does the newborn go from here? The net is vast and infinite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;puzzle-the-invisible-shove-it&quot;&gt;Puzzle: The Invisible Shove it&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;7reIy6lCoznfJ9RU2Ag5cNpsYrde8Roz6HVPDS52LRj6joPKEyImfaN73ZwsDDO
aL4aBwOu+OOZKKZ6//y4IAam2RpQXYYyC/OKYEUqZqtR1F3b0cI9a4/O5vcn3JA
xGnBVi1hlfZJ5+y9EtJuZWUng==
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>esac-io</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="hello virtual world" /><summary type="html">Well, everyone knows how hard writing can be (even more challenging in another language far aside from you mother one), so this is a attempt to improve this particular skill, and spread some information in the data sea which currently compose majority of VIRTUALITY.</summary></entry></feed>