<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-03-17T17:33:02-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Hidden Ones</title><subtitle></subtitle><author><name>esac-io</name></author><entry><title type="html">Hello world</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/2020/03/15/hello-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello world" /><published>2020-03-15T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-03-15T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/2020/03/15/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/posts/2020/03/15/hello-world.html">&lt;p&gt;Well, everyone knows how hard writing can be (even more challenging
using a foreign language), so this blog was created as an attempt
to improve this skill and as a side effect: add a little bit more
information to the data sea called &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;VIRTUALITY&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other goals: having an online presence and an easy platform
for publishing, avoiding usual self-sabotage!
Beware though, blog posts are just daydreams
from a troubled, disruptive and lazy mind, nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;virtuality&quot;&gt;Virtuality&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yes, the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;artificial&lt;/code&gt; world that surrounds our existence is
growing at exponential rates. Virtual interfaces already are
the main bridge used to access the present, understand the past,
unveil the future, all beings, all things, interlinked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the decline/eminent collapse of western civilization,
a clear horizon is blossoming, its almost palpable, alive,
breathing, expanding, taking form, nothing and everything at the same time,
existential detachment, history in the making, a unstoppable force
that will obliterate every obsolete obstacle in its path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question is: &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;How disposable am I?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;And where does the newborn go from here? The net is vast and infinite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-invisible-shove-it-crackme&quot;&gt;The Invisible Shove it (crackme!)&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;7reIy6lCoznfJ9RU2Ag5cNpsYrde8Roz6HVPDS52LRj6joPKEyImfaN73ZwsDDO
aL4aBwOu+OOZKKZ6//y4IAam2RpQXYYyC/OKYEUqZqtR1F3b0cI9a4/O5vcn3JA
xGnBVi1hlfZJ5+y9EtJuZWUng==
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>esac-io</name></author><category term="posts" /><category term="hello virtual world" /><summary type="html">Well, everyone knows how hard writing can be (even more challenging using a foreign language), so this blog was created as an attempt to improve this skill and as a side effect: add a little bit more information to the data sea called VIRTUALITY. Other goals: having an online presence and an easy platform for publishing, avoiding usual self-sabotage! Beware though, blog posts are just daydreams from a troubled, disruptive and lazy mind, nothing more.</summary></entry></feed>